## **A** CAREER PROFILE

I have been working as a back-end web developer since. I have a love of clean, elegant styling and I have lots of experience in the production of modern websites. I love creating awesome as per my clients' need. I think user experience when I try to craft something for my clients. Making a design awesome.



# Lam Ngoc Khuong

Backend Developer

## EXPERIENCES

**Lecturer - Trainer** 

09/2015 - 06/2018

Vinaenter Academy

Training for my student Java knowledge

Java Developer

05/2018 - Present

Sun\* Inc.

Build projects for clients with my team

me@ngockhuong.com (mailto:me@ngockhuong.com)

#84 987199439 (tel:+84 987199439)

lamngockhuong (https://t.me/lamngockhuong)

dev.ngockhuong.com (http://dev.ngockhuong.com)

In lamngockhuong (https://linkedin.com/in/lamngockhuo

lamngockhuong (http://github.com/lamngockhuong)

@lamngockhuong (https://twitter.com/@lamngockhuong

Resume PDF
(https://cv.ngockhuong.com/resume.p

### PROJECTS

Updating...

Virtual Coin Exchange (Japan) - Build APIs for coin exchange platform.

## **PUBLICATIONS**

Updating...

Updating...

# SKILLS & PROFICIENCY

Java & Frameworks

#### **EDUCATION**

Information Technology
Da Nang University of Education
10/2014 - 05/2018

I Java Programming Language
PHP & Frameworks
I Vinaenter Academy
07/2015 - 12/2015

Android
I LANGUAGES
RDBMS, ORDBMS & NoSQL
I Vietnamese (Native)

Javascript
English (Secondary)

I HTML5 & CSS
I INTERESTS
Coding
Watching cartoon